Guide to the George Borchardt Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III:
  - English Language Publishers, Agents, and Subjects
    - Watt, A,P. & Son DeBono, Edward (Box 200)
    - Watt, A,P. & Son Hedberg, Hakan (Box 200)
    - Watt, A,P. & Son Raban, Jonathon (Box 201)
    - Watt, A,P. & Son Sillitoe, Alan (Box 201)
    - Weidenfeld & Nicolson Ltd Calmette, Joseph (Box 201)
    - Wolff, Helen & Kurt Books (Box 201)
  - French Language Authors, Publishers and Agents
    - Adrienne (Box 201)
    - Albin Michel Editions (Box 201)
    - Arthaud, B. Editeur (Box 201)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions 1973, 1977, 1979 (Box 201)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Offerings, 1974, 1979 (Box 201)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Breton (Box 202)
    - Balland, Andre Editions (Box 202)
    - Belfond, Pierre Editions 1974/1975 (Box 202)
    - Belfond, Pierre Editions Offerings, 1974/1975 (Box 202)
    - Berg International Editions 1974 (Box 202)
    - Berg International Editions Offerings, 1975 (Box 202)
    - Blais, Marie-Claire (Box 202)
    - Bourgeois - U.G.E. (Union Generale d'Editions) (Box 202)
    - Buchet-Chastel Editions (Box 202)
    - Cendrars, Blaise (Box 202)
    - Cerf, Editions du 1974 (Box 202)
    - Cerf, Editions du Ganoczy (Box 202)
    - Champ Libre Editions 1915 (Box 202)
    - Champ Libre Editions Politiques des Auteurs (Box 202)
    - Charles-Roux, Edmonde (Box 202)
    - Crepax, Guido (Box 203)
    - Delattre, Sa1 (Agent) (Box 203)
    - Denoel 1975-1977 (Box 203)
    - Denoel Offerings, 1975, 1977 (Box 203)
    - DDE (Desclee de Brouwer), 1972, 1977 (Box 203)
    - DDE (Desclee de Brouwer) Offerings, 1979 (Box 203)
    - Euredif (Box 203)
    - Flamniarion 1915 (Box 203)
    - Flamniarion Offerings, 1975, 1978 (Box 203)
    - Ghnassia, Maurice (Box 2O4)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions 1973-1977 (Box 204)
    - Lapautre, Michelle, Literary Agent 1962, 1965, 1966, 1974, 1977 (Box 204)
    - Lapautre, Michelle 1978, 1980 (Box 205)
    - Lapautre, Michelle Correspondence, 1963, 1964 (Box 205)
    - Lapautre, Michelle Grove Press (Box 205)
    - Lapautre, Michelle Little Brown Company (Box 205)
    - Lapautre, Michelle Pollinger (Box 206)
    - Maspero, Francois, Editeur 1969-1974 (Box 206)
    - Maspero, Francois, Editeur Offerings, 1972 (Box 206)
    - Maspero, Francois, Editeur Offerings, 1973/1974 (Box 207)
    - Monteilhet, Hubert, 1974 (Box 207)
    - Monteilhet, Hubert Foreign Rights, 1974 (Box 207)
    - Nouvel Observateur (Box 207)
    - Pauvert, Jean-Jaques, Editions, 1963-1966 (Box 207)
    - Pauvert, Jean-Jaques, Editions, 1967-1970 (Box 208)
    - Payot, Editions, l964-1967; 1969 (Box 208)
    - Payot, Editions Offerings, 1971 (Box 208)
    - Plon, Librairie, 1964-1966, 1971-1976 (Box 209)
    - P.U.F. (Presses Universitaires de France) (Box 209)
    - Seghers, Editions, 1963, 1966 (Box 209)
    - Seuil, Editions du, 1966-1969 (Box 210)
    - Seuil, Editions du, 1970-1972 (Box 211)
    - Seuil, Editions du (1), 1973-1975 (Box 212)
    - Seuil, Editions du (2), 1975 -1977 (Box 213)
    - Seuil, Editions du Aubier, Dominique (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Barreau, Jean-Claude (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Bauchet, Pierre (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Bernanos, Georges (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Berque, Jacques (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Brien, Andre (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Chenu, M.-D. (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Crouzat, Henri (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Cuenot, Claude (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Danielou, Father (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Dormann, Geneviere (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Dumitriu, Petru (Box 214)
    - Seuil, Editions du Dumont, Rene (Box 215)
    - Seuil, Editions du Godbout, Jacques (Box 215)
    - Seuil, Editions du Gorz, Andre (Box 215)
    - Seuil, Editions du Jacquemard, Simone (Box 215)
    - Seuil, Editions du Jean, Marcel (Box 215)
    - Seuil, Editions du Journal de l'Eglise (Box 215)
    - Seuil, Editions du Journet, Charles (Box 215)
    - Seuil, Editions du Integrale (Box 215)
    - Seuil, Editions du Lacouture, Jean & Simone (Box 215)
    - Seuil, Editions du Leon-Dufour, Xavier (Box 216)
    - Seuil, Editions du Lorraine, Michelle (Box 216)
    - Seuil, Editions du Lubac, Henri de (Box 216)
    - Seuil, Editions du Maitree Spirituels (Box 216)
    - Seuil, Editions du Marrou, Henri (Box 216)
    - Seuil, Editions du Microcosme, 1959-l964 1966, 1969-1970 (Box 216)
    - Seuil, Editions du Offerings, 1966 (Box 217)
    - Seuil, Editions du Perrin, Henri (Box 217)
    - Seuil, Editions du Pezeril, Abbe (Box 217)
    - Seuil, Editions du Salaun, R. & Marcus, R. (Box 217)
    - Seuil, Editions du Senghor, Sedar (Box 217)
    - Seuil, Editions du Simon, Boris (Box 217)
    - Seuil, Editions du Solfeges (Box 217)
    - Seuil, Editions du Sollers, Phillippe (Box 217)
    - Seuil, Editions du Teilhard de Chardin (Box 218)
    - Seuil, Editions du Tresmontant, Claude (Box 218)
    - Seuil, Editions du Viansson-Ponte, Pierre (Box 218)
    - Seuil, Editions du Zodiaque (Box 218)
    - Table Ronde, 1962, 1964, 1965 (Box 218)
  - Other Foreign Rights and Agents
    - Agencia Literaria Carmen Balcells, Barcelona, 1971, 1977, 1980 (L - Z) (Box 219)
    - Gans, Alexander Literair Agent, The Netherlands, 1977 (Box 219)
    - Havas, Laslo, Munich (Box 219)
    - Israel (Box 219)
    - Japan UNT Agency, Inc. Tokyo, 1977, 1978 (Box 220)
    - Linder, Erich Agenzia Letteraria Internazionale, Milan, 1980 (Box 220)
    - Mohrbooks Literary Agency, Zurich, 1971, 1978, 1980 (Box 220)
    - Sane, Lennart Agency, Malmo, Sweden, 1978, 1979, 1980 (Box 221)
    - Turkey (Agents) (Box 221)
- Series IV
  - English Language Publishers, Agents and Subjects
    - Cape Ltd. Pym, Barbara (Box 222)
    - Hutchinson Ltd. General Correspondence (Box 222)
    - Hutchinson Ltd. Rendell, Ruth (Box 222)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Aveline, Claude (Box 222)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Bail, Murray (Box 222)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Beeching, Jack (Box 222)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Franklyn, Julian (Box 223)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Hogarth, Paul (Box 223)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle James, John (Box 223)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Keneally, Thomas (Box 223)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Rule, Jane (1) (Box 223)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Rule, Jane (2) (Box 224)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Searle, Ronald (Box 224)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Seton, Marie (Box 224)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Vallejo, Antonio (Box 224)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Wantmough, David (Box 224)
    - Leresche, Hope & Sayle Watney, John (Box 224)
    - Robert Levis Rosen Associates, Ltd. (Box 225)
    - Society of Authors Representatives (Box 225)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 225)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Correspondence, 1978 - l984 (Box 226)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Adelson, Roger (Box 226)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Aldiss, Brian (1) (Box 226)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Aldiss, Brian (2) (Box 227)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Alter, Stephen (Box 227)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Bermant, Chaim (Box 227)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Dead Files (Box 227)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd General (Box 228)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Goodfield, June (Box 228)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Hamilton, Elizabeth (Box 228)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Hazlehurst, Cameron (Box 228)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Johnson, Brian (Box 228)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Johnson, Thompson (Box 228)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Raban, Jonathan (Box 228)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Raphael, Frederick (Box 228)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Scanmell, Michael (Box 228)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Tennant, Emma (Box 229)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Vaizey, John (Box 229)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Waddington, C. H. (Box 229)
    - Watt, A.P. and Son Ltd Zohar, Dana (Box 229)
  - French Language Publishers, Agents and Subjects
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Anozie, Sunday (Box 229)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Audet, J.P. (Box 229)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Bouillard, Henri (Box 229)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Folz, Robert (Box 229)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Ladriere, Jean (Box 229)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Marin, Louis (Box 229)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Nabert, Jean (Box 229)
    - Aubier Montaigne Editions Simonis, Yvan (Box 229)
    - Belfond, Pierre Editions Dumas, F.R. (Box 229)
    - Belfond, Pierre Editions Renoir, Jean (Box 229)
    - Benveniste, Emile (Box 229)
    - Bernard, Michel (Box 229)
    - Bettleheim, Charles (Box 229)
    - Billetdoux, Francois (Box 230)
    - Blaisdell French Literature (Box 230)
    - Bouyer, Louis (Box 230)
    - Buchet - Chastel Editions Rivald, Regis (Box 230)
    - Butor, Michel (Box 230)
    - Carouges, Michel (Box 230)
    - Chauvet, Marie (Box 230)
    - Chevallier, Gabriel (Box 230)
    - Coccioli, Carlo (Box 230)
    - Colin, Armand (Box 230)
    - Coste, Didier (Box 230)
    - Delpire Editeur (Box 230)
    - Denoel Editions Behimer, Hans (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Del Vasto, Lanza (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Delvaux, Paul (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Desmarest, Marie-Anne (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Etcherelli, Claire (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Godard, Jean-Luc (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Groult, Flora (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Groussard, Serge (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Japrisot, Sebastien (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Kantof, Albert (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Leger, Fernand (Box 231)
    - Denoel Editions Planete Encyclopedia (Box 232)
    - Denoel Editions Pons, Maurice (Box 232)
    - Denoel Editions Sauvy, Alfred (Box 232)
    - Denoel Editions Sempe, Jean-Jacques (Box 232)
    - Denoel Editions Servan - Schrefber, Jean-Jacques (Box 232)
    - Denoel Editions Thomas, Louis (Box 232)
    - Derrida, Jacques (Box 232)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Bellet, Maurice (Box 232)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Corbon, Jean (Box 232)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) de la Croix, Paul-Marie (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Drioton, Etienne (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Durandeaux, Jacques (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Les Ecrivains Devant Dieu (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Feuillet, A. (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Guillet, Jacques (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Hostie, Raymond (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Janssens, Louis (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Jean-Nesmy, Claude (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Labarriere, P.J. (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Lacombe, Olivier (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Latourelle, Rene (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Lefebvre, Georges (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Lubienska de Lanval, Helene (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Maik, Henri (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Monden, Louis (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) La Mystique et Les Mystiques (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Philipon, A. (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Rigaux, Beda (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Sabourin, L. (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Smulders, Pierre (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Symposia (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Trooster, S. (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Uleyn, Arnold (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) van Caster, M. (Box 233)
    - DDB (Desclee de Brouwer) Wynants, Michel (Box 233)
    - Descroche, Henri (Box 234)
    - Des Femmes Forrest, Eva (Box 234)
    - Dommerques, Pierre (Box 234)
    - Editions Universitaires (Box 234)
    - Fasquelle Music Ehcyclopedia (Box 234)
    - Librarie Fayard (Box 234)
    - Fejto, Francois (Box 234)
    - Flammarion Offerings, 1919 (Box 234)
    - Flammarion Ruffie, Jacques (Box 234)
    - Flammarion Theodorakis, Mikis (Box 234)
    - Foucoult, Michel (Box 234)
    - Friedlander, Saul (Box 235)
    - Friedman, Georges (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editions Aragon, Louis (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Artaud, Antonin (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Ayme, Marcel (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Bachelard, Gaston (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Berque, Jacques (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Bregeon, Janine (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Bruckberger (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Burnier, Michel Antoine (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Cabanis, Jose (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Cau, Jean (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Chazal, Malcolm (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Claudel, Paul (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Cioran, E.M. (Box 235)
    - Gallimard Editiones Decroux, Etienne (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Duverger, Maurice (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Gilles, Daniel (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Goldstein, David (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Groethuysen, Bernard (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Guerin, Daniel (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Guyotat, Pierre (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Kahnweiler, Daniel (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Kern, Alfred (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Lange, Monique (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Le Clezio, J.M.G. (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Leiris, Michel (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Martin, Charles-Noel (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Merle, Robert (1) (Box 236)
    - Gallimard Editiones Merle, Robert (2) (Box 237)
    - Gallimard Editiones Merleau-Ponty, Maurice (Box 237)
    - Gallimard Editiones Meyer, Jean (Box 237)
    - Gallimard Editiones Michelet (Box 237)
    - Gallimard Editiones Mohrt, Michel (Box 237)
    - Gallimard Editiones Mousnier, Roland (Box 238)
    - Gallimard Editiones Offerings (Box 238)
    - Gallimard Editiones Pleiade, Encyclopedia (Box 238)
    - Gallimard Editiones Ponge, Francis (Box 238)
    - Gallimard Editiones Romains, Jules (Box 238)
    - Gallimard Editiones Rostand, Jean (Box 238)
    - Gallimard Editiones Semprun, Jorge (Box 238)
    - Gallimard Editiones Starobinski, Jean (Box 238)
    - Gallimard Editiones Thomas, Edith (Box 238)
    - Garaudy, Roger (Box 238)
    - Gascar, Pierre (Box 238)
    - Gauquelin, Michel (Box 239)
    - Goldman, Lucien (Box 239)
    - Gonthier Histoire d'une Prostitute (Box 239)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Alexandre, Philippe (Box 239)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Aron, Robert (Box 239)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Ayme, Marcel (Box 239)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Bars, Henry (Box 239)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Berger, Yves (Box 239)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Charles-Roux, Edmonde (1) (Box 239)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Charles-Roux, Edmonde (2) (Box 240)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Cixons, Helene (Box 240)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Couteaux, Andre (Box 240)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Duquesne, Jacques (Box 240)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Eschasseriaux, Bernard (Box 240)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Fernandez, Dominique (Box 240)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Fesquet, Henri (Box 240)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Franco, Victor (Box 240)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Girandoux, Jean (Box 240)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Girard, Rene (Box 241)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Joffrey, Pierre (Box 241)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Julien, Claude (Box 241)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Lemercier, Gregoire (Box 241)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Malraux, Clara (Box 241)
    - Grasset, Bernard Editions Monsigny, Jacqueline (Box 241)
    - Julliard offerings (Box 241)
    - Laffont offerings (Box 241)
  - Other Foreign Agents, Authors and Rights
    - Escobal, Patricio (Box 242)
    - Turkey (Box 242)
    - Tuttle Agency, Japan (Box 242)
- Series V: 1957-1984
  - ENGLISH LANGUAGE AUTHORS
    - Abrams, Linsey -- Abramsky & Collins; Chimen & Henry -- Agate, J.E. -- Alding, Peter -- Alexander, C.H. O'D -- Allsop, Kenneth -- Alter, Robert: 1979 -- Ambler, C. Gifford -- Ami, Georges -- Amiot, F. -- Anderson, Ann -- Andrew, Prudence -- Anouilh, Jean -- Arland, Marcel -- Armstrong, Gregory: 1976-1977 -- Arnaud, Cecile -- Asaro, Anne and Kraus, Pat -- Ash, William -- Asprey, Robert: 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 243)
    - Asprey, Robert: 1977 -- Asquith, Lady Cynthia -- Astrachan, Anthony: 1974-1975 -- Atkinson, Ti-Grace: 1973-1976 -- Badcock, C.R. -- Balfour, James -- Barbault, Armand -- Barber, Richard -- Barford, Philip -- Baskett, John -- Bell, Rose & Colin -- Bender, Albert K. -- Benson, Dennis C. -- Bentley, Joyce -- Berke-Barnes -- Bernard, Michel -- Berry, Francis -- Betjeman -- (Box 244)
    - Bloom, Leonard -- Boetie, Dugmore -- Bond, Brian -- Bondaryev, Yuri -- Branson, David -- Brown, Fred: 1973-1975 -- Bruckberger, R.P. -- Buchan, Tom -- Burke, Edmund -- Burr, H.S. -- Caldwell & Wood -- Calmette, Joseph -- Carswell, John -- Caute, David: 1979, 1981 -- Charyn, Jerome 1980 -- Chesser, Eustice -- Cohen, Geulah -- Cole, Martin & Cauthry, Philip -- Coleman, John -- Collins -- Collison, Edmund -- Conn, Stewart -- Copeland, James -- Craig, Bill -- Crawford, Sheilagh -- Crombie, John -- Crossley -- Crowther, J.G. -- Cunliffe, Mitzi -- Curvers, Alexis -- (Box 245)
    - Darien, Georges -- Darty, Peter -- David, Janina -- David-Neel, Alexandra -- Davies, David -- Dennis, Mary -- Dennison, George -- Dennys, Rodney -- Des Pres, Terrence: 1979 -- Dickstein, Morris: 1977, 1979 -- Dinsdale, Tim: Loch Ness Moster -- Diringer, David -- Drake, W. Raymond -- Dubchek, Alexander -- Duddington, Natalie -- Dumas, Alexandre -- Dunkell, Samuel: 1979-1980 -- Edwards, Harry -- El Masry, Yousef -- Ellerbeck, Rosemary: 1978 -- Elliott, George P.: 1970 -- (Box 246)
    - Elliott, George P.: 1971, 1975 -- Farber, Thomas -- Farga, Franz -- Feakes, G.J. -- Featherstone, Donald -- Fellowes, Catherine -- Feversham, Lord -- Field, P.J.C. -- Finch & Putnam -- Fitzgerald, C.P. -- Flamant & Singer-Kerel -- Fletcher, Geoffrey -- Franklin, Olga -- Franklyn, J. & Keeble, V. -- Fraser, Frances -- Frewer, Glyn -- Fry, Pete -- Fuller, John -- Gaby, Dan -- Gallet, Michel -- Gash, Jonathan: 1984 -- (Box 247)
    - Gasking, Elizabeth -- Gaylin, Willard: 1980 -- Geach, P.T. -- Gerassimov, M.M. -- Ghanem, Fathi -- Ghnassia, Maurice -- Gibbons, Calvin -- Gilder, George: 1977 -- Gilliatt, Penelope: 1980 -- Glasfurd, Alec -- Glaskin, G.M. -- Gloag, John: 1977 -- Godden, G.: Cancelled Contracts -- Godson, John -- Goffstein, M.B. -- (Box 248)
    - Goldberger, Paul: 1980 -- Goodman, Jonathan -- Gordon, Diana -- Gouri, Haim -- Graham, C. & Curling, B. -- Green, H. & Spencer, J.S. -- Griffiths, Kenneth -- Hadfield, John -- Hayes, M. Horace -- Hazlehurst, Cameron -- Henderson, Ian -- Herman, Zvi -- Hiebeler, Toni -- Hill, Brian -- Hill, Douglas -- Hill, Graham -- Hodson, Harry -- Hogg, Garry -- Hollins, Arthur -- Honeycombe, Gordon -- Hotteterre le Romain, J. -- Howson, Gerald -- Huggett, Richard -- Hughes, John -- Hutchinson, Beryl -- Hutton, Bernard -- Hyde, W. Lewis: 1981 -- (Box 249)
    - Hyers, M. Conrad -- Israel, Peter: 1975-1976 -- James, John -- Jones, Alick -- Jordania, Redjeb -- Joseph, Helen -- Juliano, Annette: 1978 -- Kay, Mara -- Kelly, Linda: 1976 -- Kenon, Kathleen -- King, P.E. -- Knight, Alanna -- Knox, Brian -- Kodaly, Zoltan -- Kovler, Peter -- Kramer, Hilton: 1970 -- (Box 250)
    - Kramer, Hilton: 1977-1978 -- Larney, Judith -- Latham, J.W. -- Lauder, Ian -- Lee, Arthur -- Lee, John Alan: New Press, 1977 -- Legg, Stuart -- Lelchuk, Alan: Movie Rights: 1972-1975 -- Lelchuk, Alan: Foreign Rights: 1974-1975 -- Lelchuk, Alan: 1975 -- Lelchuk, Alan: Movies: 1976 -- Levy, M. -- Lieberman, Jethro: 1975 -- (Box 251)
    - Liberman, Jethro, 1977 -- Liberman, Jethro, 1978 -- Liepmann, Klaus -- Lifar, Serge (dead) -- Linder, Mariella (dead) -- Lindsay, Cressida (dead) -- Lloyd, Ward -- Lonsdale, Gordon (cancelled) -- Lorraine, Michelle -- Lowery, Bruce, 1975 -- Ludlam, Harry -- Luisi, Billy -- Lumumba, Patrice (cancelled) -- Lunt, James (cancelled) -- MacAdams, Cynthia -- McBride, William (dead) (Box 252)
    - McCartney, James -- McCormick, Donald -- McCulloch, Alan -- McCutcheon, Hugh -- McDonnagh, Don: 1973 -- McElroy, Joan: 1975-1977 -- McElroy, Joseph: 1974-1977 -- McGough, Roger -- McIntosh, Christopher -- McLuhan, Terri: 1974 -- MacKinnon, Charles: 1976 -- (Box 253)
    - Macmillan, Norman -- Malone, John: 1975-1977, 1979 -- Malone, John: Foreign Rights -- Mander, R. & Mitchenson, J. -- Mannin, Ethel -- Manning, Jack: 1977 -- Mansfield, Kenneth -- (Box 254)
    - Marcus, Steven -- Marshall, Peter -- Martin, Kingsley -- Martucci & Ranieri -- Mason, Haydn -- Mayer, Peter -- Mead, W.R. & Brown, M.H. -- Mellow, James R. -- Mellows, Joan -- Melvill, Harold -- Miller, Jean Baker: 1975-1977 -- (Box 255)
    - Millett, Kate: Foreign Rights -- Milani, Milena -- Milner & Smart -- Mollo, John -- Montgomery, Viscount -- Moore, Bobby -- Moorse, George -- Morayk, Neville -- Morgan, Robin -- Morry, W.R. & Mitchell, W.M. -- Moseley, Maboth -- Moss, Robert -- Mossinsohn, Igal -- Mountjoy, Alan B.; Clifford Embleton -- Moury, Alain -- Moussa, Pierre -- Naydler, Merton -- Neame, L.E. -- Neuburg, Paul -- Neuhaus, H. -- Neveux, Georges -- Newfield, Jack -- Newman, Charles: 1973-1975 -- (Box 256)
    - Newman, Leslie: 1973-1975 -- Nickson, Hilda -- Noonan, Michael -- Noren, Catherine: 1976-1978 -- Norcliffe, G.B. -- Norman, Herbert & John -- Nurmi, Martin -- O'Callahan, Sean -- O'Hara, Patrick -- O'Neil & Longford -- O'Neil, William: 1974-1975 -- Oag, Shay -- Oldroyd, Harold -- Ottin, Merry -- Palley, William S. -- Park, Ruth -- Parkes, James -- Partington, Norman (Box 257)
    - Perin, Constance: 1976-1979 -- Pred, Alan -- Prentice, Robin: National Trust Guides -- Preston, Hugh -- Price, Jonathan -- Price, Norman -- Pugh, P.D. -- Pulbrook & Gould -- Pullan, J.M. -- Quayle, Eric -- Rab, Gustav -- Raban, Jonathan -- Rabinowitz, Dorothy: 1973 -- Racster, Olga -- Rae, Hugh -- Raphael, Chaim -- Ravenscroft, Trevor (Box 258)
    - Rawson, P.S. -- Raynor, Henry -- Read, Elfreida -- Reich, Tova: 1977 -- Reid, Randall: 1975 -- Rieth, Adolph -- Richer, Paul -- Rivers, Anne -- Robins, Eric -- Rogers: Chatwin, Bruce: 1977-1979 -- Plante, David: 197-1980 -- Rolt, Wheeler F. -- Romanov -- Ronson, Mavis -- Rosebury, Theodore -- Ross, Maggie -- Roth, Henry -- Roth, Oscar M.D. (Box 259)
    - Rowe, Christopher -- Rowland, Peter -- Roy, Archie -- Rubens, Alfred -- Rudorff, Raymond -- Russel, Edward -- Rutledge, Dom Denis -- Ryall, Edward -- Sagaris -- Said, Edward: 1973-1976 -- Samuel, Edwin -- St. George, George: 1975 -- Sanders, Roland: 1974, 1976 -- Sandstrom, Gosta -- Sangharakshita, Bhikshu -- Saulnier, Tony (Box 260)
    - Saxton, Martha: 1978-1979 -- Sayre, Nora: 1974 -- Schon, Donald -- Schuster & Wollseley -- Schwartz, Boris -- Scott, T. & Cousins, Geofrey -- Scott-Stokes, Henry: 1974, 1976 -- Sereny, Gita: 1978-1979 (Box 261)
    - Sheck, Laurie -- Shores, C. & Ring, H. -- Shulman, Sandra -- Sillitoe, Alan -- Silverlight, John -- Silverstone & Hyman: 1975- -- Sinclaire, Marianne -- Sitney, P. Adams -- Skelton, Geoffrey -- Slanska, Josefa -- Smith -- Snelling, O.F. -- Snow, Peter -- Solomon, Barbara Probst: 1974-1976, 1978 -- Somerfield, E.: 1977 (Box 262)
    - Spearman, Neville: Whore's Rhetorick -- Spearman, Neville: Youth Hosteller's Guide -- Sprigge, Elizabeth -- Stahl, E.L. & Yuill, W.E. -- Stasov, Vladimir -- Steiner, Irene -- Stevenson, W.C. -- Strachey, Lython -- Strangewayes-Booth -- Stuart, Forbes -- Summerson, John -- Suyin, Han -- Sykes, John -- Tack, Alfred -- Taylor, John -- Tchernine, Odette -- Temple, Nigel -- Tester, M.H. -- Thackery, Alec -- Tuten, Frederick: 1973 -- Verlet, Pierre -- Wade, R.G. -- Walder, David -- Ward, Robert: 1975 -- Warner, Dennis: 1975 (Box 263)